

Rizwan Hussain

Flutter Developer

How to reach me:

Home:

+923105037468

Cell:

+923105037468

Fmail:

chrizwanarain6@gmail.com

Linkedin:

Irizwan-hussain573636181

Adress:

GTTInstitute rich bell road Kashmirpoint , Mur

Educational Training

Intermediate:

ICS

- Enrolled since 2014 to 2016
- Taking up electives in programing with c++

PMAS Arid agriculture university Rawalpindi

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

- Attended from 2016 to 2020
- Taking up specialization courses in computer science to broaden skill set.

Personal Profile

I am a Flutter developer with robust problemsolving skills and proven experience in creating and designing Hybrid Applications in a testdriven environment. I consider myself a fast learner and a team player.

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

- Dart
- Kotlin
- JAVA
- XML
- Php

Key Skills:

- Flutter
- Firebase
- OOP
- Dart
- Debugging
- Api integration
- Bloc state management
- Github
- google maps
- postman
- Clean code
- Json Responsive UI
- Darkmode
- Localization
- Geolocator
- Map polylines
- Authentication

Career Summary

Flutter Developer

Goey Pvt Limited July 2022 to present

Windrive App:

It's online cab app deals with all type of rides with respect to passengers and riders. I worked on polylines, google maps, api integration, current location and effective UI design.

Flutter Developer

LADS Technologies 2021 February to 2022 april

IOS camera android with AWS stack:

- Camera feature
- Square camera
- Video feature
- Beauty Filters By using Camerax

Live Apps:

Check out "Contacts Backup : Recover , Transfer, Manage, Copy" https://play.google.com/store/apps/details

id=com.contacts.backup.transfer.restore.zp

Check out "iCam HD camera app: take a photo frames & slowmo"

Android Developer

Innovative Trends 2020 August 2020 November

Walkie Talkie(Kotlin):

We can send and receive voice messages to specific number or ID. Firebase is used for authentication and AWS is for saving all the data of user like phone number, name, profile photo and voice clips.

Flutter Teamlead, Goey Pvt LImited Cell: +92347-3311194